<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Phone Bill</string>
  <string name="readme">
    "\n This app is designed to track any number of customer phone \n"
    "bills. From the main menu you can select either of the \n following buttons: \n"
    "\n <b>- Help: </b>Displays this screen."
    "\n <b>- Manage Customers: </b> Create a new entry for a new customer
    \n to store their phone calls and manage them."\n

 <big><b>Manage Customers - What is it good for?\n</b></big>
    "If there are no customers currently stored, an alert message\n"
    "will be present. Tapping <b>"Add Customer"</b> will allow you to add a \n new customer to the application.\n"
 "To view and modify a customer tap the customer name.\n
    "You will be taken to a new screen that will display all stored\n"
    "calls (if present), as well as add, search and reset.\n\n"

    <big><b>Add\n</b></big>
    "This will allow you to add calls. Examples are present in each\n"
    "field, and time is in 12hr format with AM/PM options. Failure\n"
    "to enter correct format will present errors or a message at\n"
    "at the bottom informing you of the issue.\n\n"

    <big><b>Search\n</b></big>
    "Similar input requirements as add, but is used to display\n"
    "calls within a date range you have provided. The application\n"
    "will then display all calls (non-inclusive) in that date range.\n\n"

    <big><b>Reset\n</b></big>
    "Resets the view to default if search has been used.\n"
    "This is return to the list of calls back to the original\n"
    "display of showing all calls of that customer in ascending\n"
    "order.\n\n"
    "\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t<big><big><big><b>Enjoy!</b></big></big></big>"


    </string>
  <string name="help">Help</string>
  <string name="customers_activity_ab_title">Customer List</string>
  <string name="manage_customers">Manage Customers</string>
  <string name="phone_bill_manager_5001">Phone Bill Manager 5001</string>
  <string name="customer_list_is_empty">
        Customer list is empty! Click \"Add Customer\" to update this list.
    </string>
  <string name="add_customer">Add Customer</string>
  <string name="customer_name">Customer Name</string>
  <string name="submit">Submit</string>
  <string name="readme_activity_ab_title">README</string>
  <string name="main_activity_ab_title">Phone Bill - Main Menu</string>
  <string name="customer_instructions">Tap a customer to perform additional operations</string>
  <string name="empty_call_list">No calls have been saved to this customer. Click \"Add\" to update this list.\n
        Search will be enabled once a call is added.</string>
  <string name="add_call">Add</string>
  <string name="search_call">Search</string>
  <string name="reset">Reset</string>
  <string name="divider">divider</string>
  <string name="info_input_tip">Enter the information for the phone call you wish to add</string>
  <string name="input_hint_caller">Caller Phone Number</string>
  <string name="input_hint_callee">Callee Phone Number</string>
  <string name="start_date_and_time">Start Date and Time</string>
  <string name="end_date_and_time">End Date and Time</string>
  <string name="mm_dd_yyyy">mm/dd/yyyy</string>
  <string name="hh_mm">hh:mm</string>
  <string name="how_calls_are">Below are calls in this bill, in ascending order by date</string>
  <string name="search_tip">Enter the date and time you want to search for calls</string>
</resources>